{
    "subject": "resource/Kirk_Fordice",
    "predicate": "ontology/militaryRank",
    "object": "resource/Colonel",
    "human_readable": "Kirk Fordice held the rank of Colonel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8229702115058899,
            "question": "Was Kirk Fordice a high-ranking officer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7087551951408386,
            "question": "What was Kirk Fordice's military rank?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5473917126655579,
            "question": "Are there different ranks within a Colonel's position?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.448894739151001,
            "question": "Can someone reach the rank of Colonel through training and experience?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4344177842140198,
            "question": "Could Kirk Fordice have commanded soldiers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4307202696800232,
            "question": "What is the typical career path for someone who achieves the rank of Colonel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3141949772834778,
            "question": "What branch of the military did Kirk Fordice serve in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30326610803604126,
            "question": "How does a Colonel's rank compare to that of a General?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2510201334953308,
            "question": "What responsibilities might a Colonel have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21128597855567932,
            "question": "Are there any specific skills needed to be a Colonel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kirk Fordice held the rank of Colonel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4921_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What responsibilities might a Colonel have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4921_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does a Colonel's rank compare to that of a General?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4921_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What branch of the military did Kirk Fordice serve in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4921_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4921_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the documents, I can see that the information about Kirk Fordice supports the triple.\n\nHere is my answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state, \"Fordice then served two years\u2019 active duty with the US Army, followed by eighteen years in the Army Reserve, retiring with the rank of colonel in 1977.\" This supports that Kirk Fordice held the rank of Colonel."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}